So, Labella has been a great partner for
us on this project. Their scope started
kind of narrow and specific and really
expanded as the project needs went
along. It's a nice sunny day. It's a
little chilly out here. Today, we're
going to look a little bit at the
exterior. We're going to do a sitewalk
and talk a little bit about some civil
engineering. Behind me, we can go up is
that the facade and the last metal
panels are very close to being done. So,
that's a pretty big milestone for us.
all the attention to the snow melt
system, all that water we're pulling out
of the building, had to bring it all the
way across Abbott, then to the creek.
>> Yeah. And especially with the the field
of play being 35 ft below grade, we got
to somehow take that water and get it
out. So, there's a a giant pump room in
the stadium.
>> That's right.
>> And then it pumps it out to to grade and
then connects to the the sewer going
down, you know, the one Bill's Drive
there and and out to Smokes Creek.
>> Yeah. and then working with you and then
with populace and their site team to
turn those into parklike settings. The
function of it has to happen and then
the form around it a lot different than
what just the mass of
>> mass sea of asphalt. Yeah, this is this
is more of an experience and
>> um you know more of an aesthetic view.
>> Yeah, we're creating a park public park.
>> Public park be taking my kids here for
sure.
>> In uh you know a couple months we're
going to get the first arrival of the
smallest statue is going to kind of go
in the middle. So you can see that we
poured all this last year and then all
the integrated lighting, all the
integrated sound. There's so much that
that's happened underground that that's
your world, right? That throughout and
the the ring of honor around us. So this
is going to be a real hot bed of
activity. Our game presentation people
and our events crew is working on like
how do we bring this all to life um come
the fall.
>> You know, one of the big things about
Buffalo and going to a game is the
experience of it. not just the game
itself, but you know, the 8 hours before
the game and it's a full uh day or
weekend experience and um you know, so
one of the things that you know,
populace and in the Bills had wanted was
larger the larger parking stalls. So,
you know, normal parking spot is 9 by8.
Uh here we've got 9x8 with a a 10 ft
area behind your stall for the for the
tailgating. Another big difference with
the the parking lot here is we've got
those walkways, you know, going in
directly into the gates kind of radial
out from the stadium and I think there's
there's six of them. So, you know,
rather than having the fans come walk
through the parking lot to get to the
gate, you have these designated areas so
it'll be much safer for fans.
>> You know, working with populace too is
that we were trying to figure that out
for day one, but then expansion down the
road. How do those prominads of the
boulevard radiate out into other
properties? So, that
>> Yeah, that's that's really exciting. and
and Labella actually is working on the
comprehensive plan for Ory Park. And you
know, we're excited to keep working on
this for the next few years.
This is where the players will be
walking through. So fans on the on the
outside of that, this is a whole video
system. So we're in the field club. This
is the first area that's really been,
you know, turned over to us. High level
of completion here. Floor, lighting,
sound system, no furniture yet.
Obviously, the bar, we're not pouring
anything yet. We're not cooking anything
yet, but we're very close. The lighting,
so it looks pretty cool. We haven't had
the opportunity to come in and light
this room. So, this room can become
anything we want it to be. We can
gradate the light from red to blue. So,
the room kind of changes and morphs.
This is really cool. The entry in here,
if you're a customer here, you're going
to park on that prominade that we walk
that we basically where we parked. You
walk in and then this is your access in
to the building. and that you're just in
and out and it's such a the experience
in and out is just completely different.
That whole entry experience, there's
nothing like it next door, right? And
there's very few like it, you know, in
all of the travels that we've had. So,
this is a highlight. This is a very
premium space. You're sitting on the 50
yard line on the home side. So, the
level, the expectations are very, very
high. And you can see it's coming
together.
The complexity of the ceiling that we've
created here is extremely difficult. So
the idea is that the lockers kind of
form and come together and then the
light bars connect it all. So everything
kind of feels connected like a team. So
right now there it's not illuminated.
The only things that are illuminated are
the fins or we're calling them the
lockers themselves and then the lighting
going down on the floor. But the real
star of the show is the ceiling lighting
and it's birectional. So, we can make
the ceiling one color and the floor a
different color. We have the ability to
customize a locker to the to the uniform
or anything else we want. So, on a game
where we're all white, the whole thing
becomes white, including the numbers.
So, like in here, it'll say 17 in white
if he's wearing white. If it's blue, if
it's the any combination we have, and
then the ceiling in the room does that
as well. The question of what does it
feel like? I'm feel like the luckiest
guy in the world. I mean, if you can
have a job where you can dream something
up and then be able to walk through it,
like for me, there's nothing nothing
better.